A Guide to the Lynchburg, Virginia, business ledgers, 1874-1909
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Lynchburg, Virginia, Business Ledgers 1874-1909
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11453
The collections consists of twenty volumes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection was given to the Library by Jerry Showalter, December 28, 1998.
Scope and Content Information
The collection includes journals and ledgers of Albert Miller Company; merchandise cash books of J. B. Lee; ledgers of Lynchburg Grocery Incorporated; and a day book of James H. Williams detailing work by farm hands; together with day books of M. D. Ray and Son of Pedlar Mills, (Amherst County) Virginia.
Contents List
- Journal: [Albert Miller Company] 1901-1902 (Box Box 1)
- Ledger: Albert Miller Company 1902-1903 (Box Box 1)
- Ledger: [Albert Miller Company] 1906-1908 (Box Box 1)
- Cash Book: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1895-1901 (Box Box 1)
- Cash Book: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1901-1902 (Box Box 1)
- Cash Book: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1902-1903 (Box Box 1)
- Cash Book: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1903-1904 (Box Box 2)
- Cash Book: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1908-1909 (Box Box 2)
- Journal: Dr. J. B. Lee, Lynchburg 1908-1909 (Box Box 3)
- Register: Lynchburg Grocery Company 1908 Jul-Dec (Box Box 3)
- Day Book: M. D. Ray & Son, Pedlar Mills 1887-1892 (Box Box 3)
- Day Book: M. D. Ray & Son, Pedlar Mills 1902-1903 (Box Box 4)
- Day Book: M. D. Ray & Son, Pedlar Mills 1906-1908 (Box Box 4)
- Ledger: [Lynchburg Grocery Incorporated], with index 1901
- Ledger: [Lynchburg Grocery Incorporated]1902 1902
- Ledger: [Lynchburg Grocery Incorporated] 1903
- Ledger: Lynchburg Grocery Incorporated 1907-1908
- Day Book: M. D. Ray & Son, Pedlar Mills 1905-1906
- Day Book: M. D. Ray & Son, Pedlar Mills 1908-1909
- Day Book: James H. Williams 1874, 1887